<resources>
    <string name="app_name">ActivitesandIntent-CodingChallenge</string>
    <string name="button_2">Text Two</string>
    <string name="button_1">Text One</string>
    <string name="button_3">Text Three</string>
    <string name="display_one">We can all think of at least one song that, when we hear it, triggers an emotional response. It might be a song that accompanied the first dance at your wedding, for example, or a song that reminds you of a difficult break-up or the loss of a loved one.
        “We have a such a deep connection to music because it is ‘hardwired’ in our brains and bodies,” Barbara Else, senior advisor of policy and research at the American Music Therapy Association told Medical News Today. “The elements of music – rhythm, melody, etc. – are echoed in our physiology, functioning and being.”
        Given the deep connection we have with music, it is perhaps unsurprising that numerous studies have shown it can benefit our mental health. A 2011 study by researchers from McGill University in Canada found that listening to music increases the amount of dopamine produced in the brain – a mood-enhancing chemical, making it a feasible treatment for depression.
        And earlier this year, MNT reported on a study published in The Lancet Psychiatry that suggested listening to hip-hop music – particularly that from Kendrick Lamar – may help individuals to understand mental health disorders.
        But increasingly, researchers are finding that the health benefits of music may go beyond mental health, and as a result, some health experts are calling for music therapy to be more widely incorporated into health care settings.
        In this Spotlight, we take a closer look at some of the potential health benefits of music and look at whether, for some conditions, music could be used to improve – or even replace – current treatment strategies. </string>

    <string name="display_two">This introduction to photography is written for beginners, with several tips and suggestions to take your skills as far as possible. However, writing an introduction to photography is like writing an introduction to words; as amazing and important as it is, photography can be almost limitlessly complex. What separates inspiring photographs from ordinary ones, and how can you improve the quality of your own work? This article lays a foundation to answer to those questions and more. Photography is the art of capturing light with a camera, usually via a digital sensor or film, to create an image. With the right camera equipment, you can even photograph wavelengths of light invisible to the human eye, including UV, infrared, and radio.
    Photography is the art of taking pictures with a device called a camera. These pictures can be either stored as a soft copy or they can be printed on photographic papers, into copies called photographs. Till a few decades ago, photography was an entirely different process of work. This was the way photography was invented. The cameras were all non-digital cameras, that used to have photographic film, and through the camera lens, lighted images used to get exposed on the film. When this exposed film was developed using special photographic chemicals, they used to lead to photography negatives, which when developed on photographic printer used to produce photographs. This process used to take a few days generally.
The modern world of Photography is through Digital cameras. These digital cameras directly capture the image through the camera lenses as softcopies or digital copies in the camera. The software of the camera is like a computer, that can store all these images or you can transfer them onto your laptop or computer. The modern mobile phones also have an excellent digital camera, with which you can practice your photography skills at ease.
        Photography has become an omnipresent art and activity today. It has moved from being a specialized art in the hands of a skilled photographer, to being a daily use activity in the hands of each and every common man.</string>
    <string name="display_three">Ever been outside for a picnic with your parents and felt excited? That is the feeling of Adventure. It reduces the monotony of the simple life that we have all selected for ourselves. A short hike with friends or a new bike can instil feelings of great joy in children. It has been told by several researchers that adventures can be useful for the increases mental functions and capacity. The child may be enthusiastic about going outdoors in these times of a global pandemic. That is not a very welcome option now. The parents must try to create the options of having indoor games. A sleepover can also be a new exciting thing for kids of this age to do. It not only brings the thrill related to Adventure but also gives the children some respite. Adventures can bring several happy memories to the people who want to embark on one. Several activities can be adventurous. Adventures include making happy memories. These memories can be cherished and looked up to in time of distress. Going out on a short trip with friends is exciting. Adventure camps are regularly initiated by several schools. The students who are involved in these activities are generally guides and scouts. The activities involved are adventure camps, bonfires and tent activities. Some of the activities that are considered adventurous can be listed. Water activities like zorbing, skiing in the water are fun. Fishing can be a fun activity for many. Some might find hiking to unknown places adventurous. Adventure is mostly related to knowing the unknown. It gives the person hope to look at something new and exciting. A bonfire is an excellent beginning for adventures. A warm cup of hot chocolate and bonfire dances are great forms of enjoyment for the vagabond heart. Playing instruments can be considered as a fun activity during a bonfire. The escape from the mundane activities of life instigates the thirst for Adventure.</string>
</resources>